Guide to the Carl Aldo Marzani Papers TAM 154
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Nonprint Materials, 1938-1990
  This series consists of eleven black and white and color portraits and snapshots of Carl Marzani, his first wife, Edith Eisner (aka Edith Emerson), and his second wife, Charlotte Pomerantz, from the middle/late 1930s through the late 1980s. It also contains three newspaper and magazine clippings illustrated with photographs of Carl and Edith Marzani or Carl Marzani. The first two concern the Marzanis' round-the-world hitch-hiking journey during 1938, the second is a portrait of Carl Marzani from U.S. News and World Report, in March 1990. The series also contains a plaque given to Marzani in 1992 from Mark Lane and a recording of Carl and Charlotte's wedding on November 12, 1966.
  - Photographs, 1938-1990 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Plaque, Oct 1992 (Box 40)
  - Recording of Carl and Charlotte's Wedding Ceremony, Nov 12, 1966 (Box 40)